hughes.net 2011-12-22

# Hughes Subscriber Privacy Policy

| 

**Hughes Subscriber Privacy Policy**

Last Updated October 1, 2008

This notice (the “Subscriber Privacy Policy”) describes the privacy policy of Hughes Network Systems, LLC (HUGHES) as it relates to Hughes' HughesNet® service (the "Service"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to the use of Hughes’ Websites at [www.hughes.com](http://www.hughes.com/), [www.hughesnet.com](http://www.hughesnet.com/), [www.gethughesnet.com](http://www.gethughesnet.com/), and any other site maintained or operated by Hughes (collectively, the “Website”). The privacy policies applicable to your use of the Website is available on our Public Website Privacy Policy page.

Hughes is committed to protecting the privacy of its subscribers. This Privacy Policy governs only Hughes’ treatment of information about subscribers to Hughes’ HughesNet service. By applying for or continuing to use the Service, you agree to the terms of this Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any goods or services controlled by third parties, even if those third parties are partners of Hughes. 

Hughes reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify or change this Privacy Policy at any time with or without prior notice to you. You should visit this page to review the current Privacy Policy on a regular basis. The date of the last update will be posted at the top of this Privacy Policy for your convenience. Your continued use of the Service following the posting of any changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes your full acceptance of those changes. 

**Information Collection and Use**

When you apply to become a subscriber of the Service, and at certain times throughout your relationship with Hughes, Hughes will ask you for personal information such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address, and financial information such as your credit card information. In addition to the information you provide, Hughes may obtain additional information about you from other sources. The information you provide to Hughes, and the information Hughes obtains about you (collectively, your “Personal Information”), may be used (1) for billing and collections purposes; (2) to provide you with the products and services you request; (3) to anticipate and resolve problems with our products and services; (4) to process and respond to inquiries; (5) to contact you about products and services that may be of interest to you; and (6) for other purposes communicated to you at the time you provide or authorize the use of the information. Hughes does not rent, sell, or share your Personal Information with third parties other than as set forth herein.

**Additional Information Disclosures**

Hughes may also use or disclose information about you, including your Personal Information, under the following circumstances: 

  * To enforce our Subscriber Agreement, Terms of Service, and/or other legal agreements; 
  * To outsource any of the tasks referenced in this Privacy Policy (e.g., billing, responding to inquiries); 
  * In response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process; 
  * To establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
  * To a company controlled by, or under common control with, Hughes for any purpose permitted by this Privacy Policy; 
  * When Hughes believes such use or disclosure is (1) necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or (2) required by law; 
  * In the future, we may sell some or all of our assets or reorganize our corporate structure. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event of a sale or reorganization of our assets, including our database, customer information may be transferred.

Hughes may use and disclose non-personal, aggregate, or summary information regarding our users without further notice. This type of information will not identify you individually.

**Updating Your Information**

If you need to update your information, please call our Customer Service department at   
1-866-347-3292 or visit customercare.myhughesnet.com and login under the "Account Information" section.

**Minors**

You must be 18 or older to apply or subscribe to the Hughes service. Hughes does not intentionally collect personal information from minors.

**Notice Regarding Hughes’ Position on Child Pornography**

Hughes takes its commitment to protect children from exploitation over the Internet extremely seriously. Consequently, Hughes is working hand-in-hand with the National Center for Missing and Exploited Children (NCMEC) and other law enforcement agencies on this important project. One of the efforts that Hughes has undertaken in this regard is to establish a specially designated email address, [cp-abuse@hughes.net](mailto:cp-abuse@hughes.net), for complaints about child pornography. Hughes further commits that all complaints received shall be investigated promptly, generally within three (3) business days or less. No Hughes facilities or services may be used by in any fashion for the transmission or dissemination of images containing child pornography.

**Security**

Hughes employs reasonable measures to protect your personal information against acquisition by unauthorized persons.

**Questions**

Please direct questions, concerns, or comments about this Privacy Policy to our email address at guest.services@hns.com. Alternatively, you may contact us at:

> Hughes Network Systems, LLC  
>  Attn: Privacy  
>  11717 Exploration Lane  
>  Germantown, MD 20876
